miniplay.com 2019-12-10

# Privacy

Starting on May 25 2018, our new Privacy Policy will become effective, according to Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).

Responsible Entity (the Owner)

Moosite S.L.  
Calle Fuencarral No.123, 8º B  
28010 Madrid (Spain)  
Tel.: +34 600 97 20 67 (not a support line)  
email: soporte @ minijuegos.com  

General

This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you about what kind of personal data we gather in order to provide our offers and internet game services, and how this data is processed and handled. Your personal data protection is very important to us.

Your data is secured against abuse and loss. We took the organizational and technical measures to make sure that our inside and outside collaborators follow these instructions regarding data protection.

This Privacy Policy contains transparent information in order to ensure that the natural persons who visit our webpage and our consumers are duly informed of the gathering, processing and use of their personal data.

Personal Data

Personal data is information regarding a natural or identifiable person (i.e. name, address, telephone number, date of birth or email address).

At Minipay.com we gather the following personal information when a user registers and starts using our Service: Name, surname(s), email, sex, date of birth, IP address and some non-personal information, such as local flash information and statistical data (browser, OS, URL that redirected to our site, date and time).

The data you provide to Miniplay.com is included in our files registered to the Spanish Data Protection Agency (hereunder , “AEPD?€). The AEPD is in charge of supervising the compliance with Spanish law about data privacy and protection and guaranteeing the privacy and security of your personal data.

You can use our online offer without providing personal data, but certain services may require said details, such as game and competition registrations.

Legal base and purpose of data processing

We gather personal information with the purposes hereunder:

  * online offer provision and contract compliance according to our Terms of Service.
  * allowing the proper identification as a User and granting access to the Services and mobile apps made available by the Owner through the data entered by the User when completing their website and/or game registration.
  * offering help when personal information is entered in order to make an inquiry.
  * successfuly completing the process when personal information is entered in order to use and/or pay for Services.
  * using said information to the extent permitted by law and the User's consent through the Owner and/or third-party ads, market research and/or statistic.
  * complying with legal regulations, particulary storage requirements.

We also process user data to the extent that it is necessary for the performance of Services or for the billing thereof. This refers in particular to game processes, game scores and information regarding the use and payment of services. We also use your data to communicate with you. This includes, in particular, the provision of assistance and support as well as the provision of important contract information. Subject to your consent, we keep you informed about news, events and promotions via e-mail.

Data protection during the application process

We collect personal data from applicants to process applications, which will be saved upon the conclusion of an agreement to implement the relationship. The legal regulations shall be considered here. In the event of a rejection, the application documentation will be deleted no later than after two months. An exception to this is, for example, if we have to retain the application documents as evidence in a legal process or if other legitimate interests exist. We will request your consent should we retain application documents in our pool of applicants for a longer period to the extent permitted by law.

Financial information

In order for some Services to be successfully completed, specifically payment procedures, the User may employ third-party services in no way related to Moosite, S.L. (Paypal, Toditocash, PaySafeCard, etc.). These third-party companies are compelled by law to handle the User's personal data in a safe and confidential manner. As such, the procedures related to the User's credit card and/or any other personal information related to payments will be directly processed by these third-party companies, therefore Moosite, S.L. will have no access to the User's credit card details and/or any other payment systems employed. For such purposes, you are advised to read the service provider's terms and conditions before starting a payment process. Should you not agree to the conditions therein stated, please do not proceed with the payment.

Consequently, the information gathered in order to complete a successful Minicoin purchase will be entered and transmitted directly by the third party responsible of the selected payment gateway. Moosite, S.L. will under no circumstances have access to the payment details. Moosite, S.L. will only access the sum deposited by the User in order to exchange the money for Minicoins.

The third-party owners of the payment services made available are exclusively responsible thereof. Moosite, S.L. takes absolutely no place in such operations; therefore you are advised to read the service provider's terms and conditions before starting a payment process. In such instances, Moosite, S.L. will be considered a third-party unrelated to such processes.

Cookies and collection of log files

Within the context of the use of our websites, forums and games, the Owner collects the following non-personal information::

  * IP addresses, time and date.
  * Cookies, local flash data.
  * Statistical information such as browser used, operating system, redirecting URL, date, time, pages used, total time of use, frequency of use.

This data is used in statistical analyses for anonymous data records and never for personal purposes.

IP addresses and the corresponding Internet information are saved for a period of maximum of six months within the scope of our legal obligations regarding data storage. Furthermore, these are stored to secure data and ensure our system fs stability and reliability. In specific situations, the Owner may also use your IP address and the corresponding Internet information to track and stop use of multiple accounts for fraudulent purposes. In cases such as these, the Owner will seek the consent for such use within the framework of the relevant game conditions.

Cookies Authorization:

Despite the fact that this is stated in the Privacy Statement, we would like to expressly inform you that we employ the use of cookies to optimize the use of our Portal and Games and Services, especially regarding user experience. By accepting out CGC, you authorize the use of cookies. At any point in the future, you can object to the use of cookies.

For all additional questions regarding cookies, please check our Cookie Policy in our Webage (http://www.miniplay.com/support/cookies)

How can you prevent the use of cookies or delete cookies?

You can disable the storage of cookies through your browser settings and delete the cookies stored in your browser at any time. However, please note that this online Service may not function, or only to a limited extent, without the use of cookies.

In addition, please note that contradictions against the creation of usage profiles work partially through opt-out cookies. Should you delete all the cookies, a contradiction may therefore no longer be taken into account and must be collected from you again.

Data transfer and service providers

Your data will be treated with the strictest confidentiality, and the Owner will not disclose it to any third parties, unless the User has given express permission to do so. We may, however, be required by law to disclose your information to an investigating authority in certain situations.

In such instances, the transfer will take place only within the framework required by the General Data Protection Regulation in art.11.:

  * The affected personal data will only be disclosed to a third party in order to complete legitimate procedures related to the Owner and the User, and only after the User has given express permission to do so.
  * The aforementioned express permission will not be necessary under these circumstances:
    * When the disclosure is authorized by Law.
    * When the affected data has been gathered from publicly available sources.
    * When the handling is related to a free and legitimate acceptance of a legal relationship whose development, compliance and/or control implies a connection with third-party registries.
    * When the addressee of the communication is an Ombudsman, the Public Authorities and/or Judges or Court in the exercise of the functions assigned to them.
  * The consent will be null and void when, for third-party personal data communications, the given information is deemed not enough for the User to fully understand the purpose for which their data will be communicated or the activities of the third party involved.

We require third parties to offer certain services in the name of the Owner. This includes, but is not limited to, payment processes through external gateways (Paypal, Toditopagos, etc.). In such instances, your data will be made available for marketing purposes, as well as for the development and improvement of the Owner's games. The aforementioned third-party companies are compelled by law to treat your data in a safe and confidential manner, and can only use said data to the extent of the fulfillment of their services. The third-party providers are only authorized to process the User's personal data in online offers in compliance with the Owner's specific instructions.

Period of storage/retention

The Owner stores your data for as long as this is necessary for the provision of our online Service and the associated services, or if we have a legitimate interest in the further storage of such. In all other cases, we will delete your personal information except for such information as we may need to maintain in accordance with contractual or statutory requirements (i.e. tax or commercial purposes, i.e. invoices). Contractual retention periods may also arise from contracts with third parties (i.e. owners of copyrights and ancillary copyrights). We will block any data that is subject to a retention period until the expiry of the relevant period..

Google Analytics

This Website uses Google Analytics, a service provided by Google Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses cookies, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the Website analyze how users utilize the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the Website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the USA. If, however, you activate the Anonymize IP option on this website, Google will remove the end of your IP address so it only locates you as within the member states of the European Union or other members of the European Economic Area. Only in rare cases will the complete IP address be transmitted to a Google server in the USA and then shortened there. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and Internet usage. The operator of this website will use information gathered via interest-related advertising as well as third-party visitor data (i.e. age, gender and interests) for the purpose of evaluation in order to find out more about the users of the Website. No personal data shall be used in this case, only a statistical evaluation of anonymous data sets shall be carried out. Google will not associate your IP address as transmitted by Google Analytics with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however, note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this Website. Furthermore, you can prohibit Google from collecting and analyzing the data generated by the cookie about your use of the Website (including your IP address) by downloading and installing the browser plugin available at http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. Should you wish to adapt or prevent the analysis of your demographic or interest-based information, you can disable Google Analytics display ads and adapt the ads in the Google Display Network: https://www.google.com/settings/ads

If you access the Website via a mobile device (smartphone, tablet, etc.) you may object to the use of your data by Google by clicking a separate link in the dialog box displayed.

Online Behavioral Advertising

The advertising on our websites will be optimized according to your predicted interests by collecting and processing anonymous data about your usage of the Website. In order to do so, third-party companies place cookies on your computer to collect user data under the Owner's name, such as when surfing the Service's webpages or when clicking an add. This allows the Owner to analyze the use of online ads and to provide you with ads that could be of interest to you and correspond to your personal preferences (Online Behavioral Advertising). No personal information, such as name, address, e-mail address etc., will be collected. IP addresses are kept anonymous so that they cannot be allocated to any specific person.

If you want to opt out of receiving Online Behavioral Advertising, you can block the placement of cookies on your computer by changing your browser settings so that it does not accept cookies.

Additionally, we permit other third parties, i.e. media agencies, to use cookies to analyze the use of online advertising and to display advertising in our Website that could be of interest to you by analyzing your personal preferences. Additionally, this should enable advertising customers to reach their target audience more accurately without large wastage. For this purpose, user statistics can, for example, be anonymously compiled and the data can be used for market research purposes, without tracing this information back to a specific person.

Social Media Plugins

Facebook

Embedded on the Website are various Facebook links. This web presence is operated exclusively by Facebook Inc., 1601 S California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA (Facebook).

Within the scope of our web presence, these links are identified by the Facebook logo or by the phrase "Like" (no Facebook plugins are used).

Should a user click one of these links, then the Facebook plugins are activated and establish a direct connection via the user fs browser to a Facebook server.

Provided that the user clicks one of the aforementioned links while visiting our website, and is logged into their personal Facebook account, the information will be forwarded to Facebook that the user has visited our website. Facebook can associate your visit to the website to your account. Facebook can associate your visit to the website to your account.

This data is transferred to and saved by Facebook. To prevent this, the user must log out of their account before clicking the link. The functions embedded in the links by Facebook, especially the transfer of data and user information, are not activated by visiting our website, but rather by clicking the corresponding links.

The purpose and scope of data collection via Facebook, the processing and use of such data, as well as your rights thereof and personal settings regarding privacy protection can be found in the Facebook privacy settings section (https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation).

For further questions pertaining to the collection, processing or use of individual user data and, regarding the disclosure, correction, blocking or deleting of data, please contact us.

Facebook Connect

The Owner offers the User the opportunity to sign up for our services through Facebook Connect. In order to do this, you will be redirected to Facebook, where you can log in using your Facebook user data. Your Facebook account will then be linked to our services. Depending on your Facebook settings, linking your account will allow the following data to be transmitted to us and/or retrieved by the Owner: name, date of birth and email address.

We shall only use this information for identification purposes and contract processing. For more information on Facebook Connect and the privacy settings, please refer to the Data Privacy Policy and Terms of Use of Facebook Inc.

Google Plus

The Website also employs the Google Plus "+1" link, which is operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, United States (Google). The link can be identified by the "+1" symbol against a white or color background.

If the User opens one of our webpages containing such a link, the User's browser establishes a direct connection to a Google server. The contents of the "+1" link are transferred directly to the User's browser, which then integrates said content in the webpage. The Owner therefore has no control over the data whatsoever that Google collects via the link, but would expect user IP addresses to be collected.

The purpose and scope of data collection via Google, the processing and use of such data, as well as your rights thereof and personal settings regarding privacy protection can be found in the Google privacy settings section https://developers.google.com/+/web/buttons-policy

If a User is a Google Plus member and does not wish to have their data collected and linked to their saved Google member data via our web presence, the user must log out of their Google Plus account before visiting our websites.

Twitter

The Website also employs the Twitter function, which is operated by Twitter, Inc. 1355 Market Street, Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103, United States (“Twitter”). These links are identified by the blue bird logo.

If the User opens one of our webpages containing such a link, the User's browser establishes a direct connection to a Twitter server. The contents of the aforementioned links are transferred directly to the User's browser, which then integrates said content in the webpage. The Owner therefore has no control over the data whatsoever that Twitter collects via the link, but would expect user IP addresses to be collected.

The purpose and scope of data collection via Twitter, the processing and use of such data, as well as your rights thereof and personal settings regarding privacy protection can be found in the Twitter privacy policy:

https://twitter.com/tos#update

If a User is a Twitter user and does not wish to have their data collected and linked to their saved Twitter user data via our web presence, the user must log out of their Twitter account before visiting our websites.

Mobile apps

The Owner's apps are provided through various app and software platforms, including the Apple App Store, the Google Play Store and social networks like Facebook. If you access, register on or use the platform or social network, personal data may be collected and used by the respective platform or social network over which the Owner basically has no influence. You will find all the relevant information in the privacy policy or privacy statement of each platform or social network.

IT security

With the help of an IT security provider, we collect and process specific data anonymously about the features of the terminal device used by the user ("device-specific data"), raw data from the TCP/IP connection and data on the use of our website by using so-called cookies and tracking technology to prevent the abuse of our services.

Initially, the IP address is also collected and processed but encrypted within a few seconds. No personal data is collected or stored. The information is stored with the IT security provider in a database for the prevention of fraud.

If, on our Website, the User concludes a contract for pecuniary interest or if the conclusion of a contract for pecuniary interest is approaching (i.e. at the beginning of the checkout process), we retrieve a risk evaluation about the terminal device you are using from the IT security provider fs database which has been stored there.

The risk evaluation is used (but not exclusively) as a basis for deciding whether a contract for pecuniary interest can be concluded.

Should it come to our attention that a user is or has attempted to abuse our services, we shall also transmit collected data to the IT security provider. In this process, however, only device-specific data, and no personal data, shall be transmitted..

Right of revocation, deletion of data

If The User has given the Owner consent to process personal data, you can withdraw this consent at any time.

The Owner deletes your personal data insofar as it is no longer needed or required, or if you have requested the deletion of this data. Please note that data cannot be deleted if there are legal or other requirements to store the data, or if we need it to bill our services.

Information on data protection, viewing information and the correction, deletion and blocking of data

For general questions regarding this privacy statement and data protection, or if you would like to query, correct, block or delete your private data in accordance with the legal stipulations, please contact us via email or post, stating your user ID, username, email address and, if applicable, your game through https://ayuda.minijuegos.com/hc/es/articles/115000091992-Quiero-eliminar-mi-cuenta You can contact us or the data protection manager directly via the contact details previously stated.

Right of appeal with the regulatory body

You have the right to file a complaint with a data protection authority. For this, you can contact the data protection authority which covers your place or residence or region.

Security provisions and technical information

All the Owner's employees receive regular training in data protection, and are committed to data protection. Our computer center and our in-house EDP department are constantly adapting the technical security precautions to the current security conditions and requirements. Both are subject to constant monitoring by our internal procedures and the data protection manager. Nevertheless, Internet technologies may have security loopholes that cannot guarantee full protection. Users can therefore submit data to us via other methods, e.g. phone.

The following technical info will enable you to adjust the privacy settings in your browser.

Internet Explorer:

For further information, visit:

http://windows.microsoft.com/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies#ie=ie-11-win-7

Mozilla Firefox:

For further information, visit:

https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-stored

Google Chrome:

For further information, visit:

https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647

Safari:

For further information, visit:

http://help.apple.com/

* * *

Date of this version: 23/05/2018 (translated)
